<resources>
    <string name="app_name">expertSub1</string>
    <string name="title_activity_list_movie">ListMovie</string>

    <string name="hello_world">Hello world!</string>
    <string name="title_avenger_end_game" translatable="false">Avenger End Game (2019)</string>
    <string name="title_parasite" translatable="false">Parasite (GisaengChung) (2019)</string>
    <string name="title_toy_story_4" translatable="false">Toy Story 4 (2019)</string>
    <string name="title_joker" translatable="false">Joker (2019)</string>
    <string name="title_the_farewell" translatable="false">The Farewell (2019)</string>
    <string name="title_booksmart" translatable="false">Booksmart (2019)</string>
    <string name="title_shazam" translatable="false">Shazam (2019)</string>
    <string name="title_glass" translatable="false">Glass (2019)</string>
    <string name="title_aquaman" translatable="false">Aquaman (2018)</string>
    <string name="title_avengerinfinity" translatable="false">Avengers: Infinity War (2018)</string>
    <string name="title_deadpool" translatable="false">Once Upon a Deadpool (2018)</string>
    <string name="title_bumblebee" translatable="false">Bumblebee (2018)</string>
    <string name="title_venom" translatable="false">Venom (2018)</string>
    <string name="title_spiderman" translatable="false">Spider-Man: Into the Spider-Verse (2018</string>
    <string name="title_dragon" translatable="false">How to Train Your Dragon: The Hidden World (2019)</string>
    <string name="overview_avenger_end_game">American superhero film based on the Marvel Comics superhero team the Avengers, produced by Marvel Studios and distributed by Walt Disney Studios Motion Pictures. It is the sequel to 2012 The Avengers, 2015 Avengers: Age of Ultron, and 2018 Avengers: Infinity War, and the twenty-second film in the Marvel Cinematic Universe (MCU). It was directed by Anthony and Joe Russo and written by Christopher Markus and Stephen McFeely, and features an ensemble cast including Robert Downey Jr., Chris Evans, Mark Ruffalo, Chris Hemsworth, Scarlett Johansson, Jeremy Renner, Don Cheadle, Paul Rudd, Brie Larson, Karen Gillan, Danai Gurira, Benedict Wong, Jon Favreau, Bradley Cooper, Gwyneth Paltrow, and Josh Brolin. In the film, the surviving members of the Avengers and their allies attempt to reverse the damage caused by Thanos in Infinity War</string>
    <string name="overview_parasite">Parasite (Korean: 기생충; Hanja: 寄生蟲; RR: Gisaengchung) is a 2019 South Korean dark comedy thriller film directed by Bong Joon-ho, who also wrote the films story and co-wrote the screenplay with Han Jin-won. The film stars Song Kang-ho, Lee Sun-kyun, Cho Yeo-jeong, Choi Woo-shik and Park So-dam, and follows a young man from a poor family who begins to tutor a rich familys daughter, and slowly starts to infiltrate their personal lives.Parasite had its world premiere at the 2019 Cannes Film Festival on 21 May 2019, where it won the Palme d Or, becoming the first Korean film to receive the award as well as the first film to do so with a unanimous vote since 2013 Blue Is the Warmest Colour. It was selected as the South Korean entry for Best International Feature Film at the 92nd Academy Awards.The film was released globally by Neon in late 2019. It earned critical acclaim and earned over $109 million worldwide, becoming Bongs highest-grossing release</string>
    <string name="overview_toy_story_4">Toy Story 4 is a 2019 American computer-animated comedy film produced by Pixar Animation Studios for Walt Disney Pictures. It is the fourth installment in Pixars Toy Story series, and the sequel to 2010 Toy Story 3. It was directed by Josh Cooley (in his feature directorial debut) from a screenplay by Andrew Stanton and Stephany Folsom; the three also conceived the story alongside John Lasseter, Rashida Jones, Will McCormack, Valerie LaPointe, and Martin Hynes. The film stars the voices of Tom Hanks, Tim Allen, Annie Potts, Tony Hale, Keegan-Michael Key, Jordan Peele, Madeleine McGraw, Christina Hendricks, Keanu Reeves, Ally Maki, Jay Hernandez, Lori Alan, and Joan Cusack.</string>
    <string name="overview_joker">Joker is a 2019 American psychological thriller film directed by Todd Phillips, who co-wrote the screenplay with Scott Silver. The film, based on DC Comics characters, stars Joaquin Phoenix as the Joker. An origin story set in 1981, the film follows Arthur Fleck, a failed stand-up comedian who turns to a life of crime and chaos in Gotham City. Robert De Niro, Zazie Beetz, Frances Conroy, Brett Cullen, Glenn Fleshler, Bill Camp, Shea Whigham, and Marc Maron appear in supporting roles. Joker was produced by Warner Bros. Pictures, DC Films, and Joint Effort in association with Bron Creative and Village Roadshow Pictures, and distributed by Warner Bros.</string>
    <string name="overview_the_farewell">The Farewell is a 2019 American comedy-drama film written and directed by Lulu Wang. It stars Awkwafina, Tzi Ma, Diana Lin, Zhao Shuzhen, Lu Hong, and Jiang Yongbo. The film follows a family who, upon learning their grandmother has only a short while left to live, decide not to tell her and schedule a family gathering before she dies. The film is based in part on director Wangs life experiences, which she first publicly discussed as part of her radio story What You Dont Know, which appeared as part of an episode of This American Life. The film was screened in the U.S. Dramatic Competition section at the 2019 Sundance Film Festival[4] and was theatrically released in the United States on July 12, 2019, by A24. It received acclaim from critics, with particular praise for Wangs screenplay and direction and the performances of Awkwafina and Zhao Shuzhen.</string>
    <string name="overview_booksmart">Booksmart is a 2019 American coming-of-age comedy film directed by Olivia Wilde (in her feature directorial debut), from a screenplay by Emily Halpern, Sarah Haskins, Susanna Fogel, and Katie Silberman. It stars Beanie Feldstein and Kaitlyn Dever as two graduating high school girls who set out to finally break the rules and party on their last day of classes; Jessica Williams, Will Forte, Lisa Kudrow, and Jason Sudeikis also star. Will Ferrell and Adam McKay executive produced the film through Gloria Sanchez Productions. The film had its world premiere at South by Southwest on March 10, 2019, and was theatrically released by United Artists Releasing in the United States on May 24, 2019, to acclaim from critics; it grossed over $24 million.</string>
    <string name="overview_shazam">Shazam! is a 2019 American superhero film based on the DC Comics eponymous character. Produced by New Line Cinema and distributed by Warner Bros. Pictures, it is the seventh installment in the DC Extended Universe (DCEU). Directed by David F. Sandberg from a screenplay by Henry Gayden, and a story by Gayden and Darren Lemke, the film stars Asher Angel as Billy Batson, a teenage boy who can transform into an adult superhero, played by Zachary Levi. Mark Strong, Jack Dylan Grazer, and Djimon Hounsou also star. The plot follows Billy Batson, who is chosen by the ancient wizard Shazam as his new champion and receives various superpowers. Billy and his best friend Freddy must discover Billy new powers in order to stop the evil Dr. Thaddeus Sivana.</string>
    <string name="overview_glass">In a series of escalating encounters, former security guard David Dunn uses his supernatural abilities to track Kevin Wendell Crumb, a disturbed man who has twenty-four personalities. Meanwhile, the shadowy presence of Elijah Price emerges as an orchestrator who holds secrets critical to both men.</string>
    <string name="overview_aquaman">Aquaman is a 2018 American superhero film based on the DC Comics character of the same name. Distributed by Warner Bros. Pictures, it is the sixth film in the DC Extended Universe (DCEU). The film was directed by James Wan, from a screenplay by David Leslie Johnson-McGoldrick and Will Beall and stars Jason Momoa as Aquaman, with Amber Heard, Willem Dafoe, Patrick Wilson, Dolph Lundgren, Yahya Abdul-Mateen II, and Nicole Kidman in supporting roles. In the film, Aquaman sets out to lead the underwater kingdom of Atlantis, replacing his half-brother, King Orm, who seeks to unite the seven underwater kingdoms against the surface world.</string>
    <string name="overview_avengerinfinity">Avengers: Infinity War is a 2018 American superhero film based on the Marvel Comics superhero team the Avengers, produced by Marvel Studios and distributed by Walt Disney Studios Motion Pictures. It is the sequel to 2012 The Avengers and 2015 Avengers: Age of Ultron, and the nineteenth film in the Marvel Cinematic Universe (MCU). It was directed by Anthony and Joe Russo, written by Christopher Markus and Stephen McFeely, and features an ensemble cast including Robert Downey Jr., Chris Hemsworth, Mark Ruffalo, Chris Evans, Scarlett Johansson, Benedict Cumberbatch, Don Cheadle, Tom Holland, Chadwick Boseman, Paul Bettany, Elizabeth Olsen, Anthony Mackie, Sebastian Stan, Danai Gurira, Letitia Wright, Dave Bautista, Zoe Saldana, Josh Brolin, and Chris Pratt. In the film, the Avengers and the Guardians of the Galaxy attempt to prevent Thanos from collecting the six all-powerful Infinity Stones as part of his quest to kill half of all life in the universe.</string>
    <string name="overview_deadpool">The film was directed by David Leitch from a screenplay by Rhett Reese, Paul Wernick, and Ryan Reynolds, who stars in the title role alongside Josh Brolin, Morena Baccarin, Julian Dennison, Zazie Beetz, T.J. Miller, Brianna Hildebrand, and Jack Kesy. In the film, Deadpool forms the X-Force to protect a young mutant from the time-traveling soldier Cable. Plans for a sequel to Deadpool began before the original film release, and were confirmed in February 2016. Though the original creative team of Reynolds, Reese, Wernick, and director Tim Miller were quickly set to return for the second film, Miller left the project in October 2016 due to creative differences with Reynolds and was soon replaced by Leitch. An extensive casting search took place to fill the role of Cable, with Brolin ultimately cast.</string>
    <string name="overview_bumblebee">On the run in the year 1987, Bumblebee finds refuge in a junkyard in a small Californian beach town. Charlie, on the cusp of turning 18 and trying to find her place in the world, discovers Bumblebee, battle-scarred and broken. When Charlie revives him, she quickly learns this is no ordinary yellow VW bug.</string>
    <string name="overview_venom">Investigative journalist Eddie Brock attempts a comeback following a scandal, but accidentally becomes the host of Venom, a violent, super powerful alien symbiote. Soon, he must rely on his newfound powers to protect the world from a shadowy organization looking for a symbiote of their own.</string>
    <string name="overview_spiderman">Miles Morales is juggling his life between being a high school student and being a spider-man. When Wilson \"Kingpin\" Fisk uses a super collider, others from across the Spider-Verse are transported to this dimension.</string>
    <string name="overview_dragon">As Hiccup fulfills his dream of creating a peaceful dragon utopia, Toothless’ discovery of an untamed, elusive mate draws the Night Fury away. When danger mounts at home and Hiccup’s reign as village chief is tested, both dragon and rider must make impossible decisions to save their kind.</string>

    <string name="tv_title_naruto_shipudden" translatable="false">Naruto Shipudden</string>
    <string name="tv_overview_naruto_shipudden">Naruto Shippuuden is the continuation of the original animated TV series Naruto.The story revolves around an older and slightly more matured Uzumaki Naruto and his quest to save his friend Uchiha Sasuke from the grips of the snake-like Shinobi, Orochimaru. After 2 and a half years Naruto finally returns to his village of Konoha, and sets about putting his ambitions to work, though it will not be easy, as He has amassed a few (more dangerous) enemies, in the likes of the shinobi organization; Akatsuki.</string>
    <string name="tv_title_supernatural" translatable="false">Supernatural</string>
    <string name="tv_overview_supernatural">When they were boys, Sam and Dean Winchester lost their mother to a mysterious and demonic supernatural force. Subsequently, their father raised them to be soldiers. He taught them about the paranormal evil that lives in the dark corners and on the back roads of America ... and he taught them how to kill it. Now, the Winchester brothers crisscross the country in their \'67 Chevy Impala, battling every kind of supernatural threat they encounter along the way.</string>
    <string name="tv_title_the_simpson" translatable="false">The Simpson</string>
    <string name="tv_overview_the_simpson">Set in Springfield, the average American town, the show focuses on the antics and everyday adventures of the Simpson family; Homer, Marge, Bart, Lisa and Maggie, as well as a virtual cast of thousands. Since the beginning, the series has been a pop culture icon, attracting hundreds of celebrities to guest star. The show has also made name for itself in its fearless satirical take on politics, media and American life in general.</string>
    <string name="tv_title_the_umbrella" translatable="false">The Umbrella</string>
    <string name="tv_overview_the_umbrella">A dysfunctional family of superheroes comes together to solve the mystery of their fathers death, the threat of the apocalypse and more.</string>
    <string name="tv_title_the_walking_dead" translatable="false">The Walking Dead</string>
    <string name="tv_overview_the_walking_dead">What did the world look like as it was transforming into the horrifying apocalypse depicted in "The Walking Dead"? This spin-off set in Los Angeles, following new characters as they face the beginning of the end of the world, will answer that question.</string>
    <string name="tv_title_shameless" translatable="false">Shameless</string>
    <string name="tv_overview_shameless">Chicagoan Frank Gallagher is the proud single dad of six smart, industrious, independent kids, who without him would be... perhaps better off. When Frank\'s not at the bar spending what little money they have, he\'s passed out on the floor. But the kids have found ways to grow up in spite of him. They may not be like any family you know, but they make no apologies for being exactly who they are.</string>
    <string name="tv_title_supergirl" translatable="false">Supergirl</string>
    <string name="tv_overview_supergirl">Twenty-four-year-old Kara Zor-El, who was taken in by the Danvers family when she was 13 after being sent away from Krypton, must learn to embrace her powers after previously hiding them. The Danvers teach her to be careful with her powers, until she has to reveal them during an unexpected disaster, setting her on her journey of heroism.</string>
    <string name="tv_title_ncis" translatable="false">NCIS</string>
    <string name="tv_overview_ncis">From murder and espionage to terrorism and stolen submarines, a team of special agents investigates any crime that has a shred of evidence connected to Navy and Marine Corps personnel, regardless of rank or position.</string>
    <string name="tv_title_riverdale" translatable="false">Riverdale</string>
    <string name="tv_overview_riverdale">Set in the present, the series offers a bold, subversive take on Archie, Betty, Veronica and their friends, exploring the surreality of small-town life, the darkness and weirdness bubbling beneath Riverdale’s wholesome facade.</string>
    <string name="tv_title_god" translatable="false">Game Of Thrones</string>
    <string name="tv_overview_god">Seven noble families fight for control of the mythical land of Westeros. Friction between the houses leads to full-scale war. All while a very ancient evil awakens in the farthest north. Amidst the war, a neglected military order of misfits, the Night\'s Watch, is all that stands between the realms of men and icy horrors beyond.</string>
    <string name="tv_title_gotham" translatable="false">Gotham</string>
    <string name="tv_overview_gotham">Everyone knows the name Commissioner Gordon. He is one of the crime world\'s greatest foes, a man whose reputation is synonymous with law and order. But what is known of Gordon\'s story and his rise from rookie detective to Police Commissioner? What did it take to navigate the multiple layers of corruption that secretly ruled Gotham City, the spawning ground of the world\'s most iconic villains? And what circumstances created them – the larger-than-life personas who would become Catwoman, The Penguin, The Riddler, Two-Face and The Joker?</string>
    <string name="tv_title_grey_anatomy" translatable="false">Grey Anatomy</string>
    <string name="tv_overview_grey_anatomy">Follows the personal and professional lives of a group of doctors at Seattle’s Grey Sloan Memorial Hospital.</string>
    <string name="tv_title_hanna" translatable="false">Hanna</string>
    <string name="tv_overview_hanna">This thriller and coming-of-age drama follows the journey of an extraordinary young girl as she evades the relentless pursuit of an off-book CIA agent and tries to unearth the truth behind who she is. Based on the 2011 Joe Wright film.</string>
    <string name="tv_title_iron_fist" translatable="false">Marvel\'s Iron Fist</string>
    <string name="tv_overview_iron_fist">Danny Rand resurfaces 15 years after being presumed dead. Now, with the power of the Iron Fist, he seeks to reclaim his past and fulfill his destiny.</string>

    <string name="tab_text_1">Movies</string>
    <string name="tab_text_2">TV Shows</string>
    <string name="title_activity_main">Movie Catalogue</string>
    <string name="change_language_settings">Change Language Settings</string>
</resources>

